question_data =[{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"&quot;Half-Life 2&quot; runs on the Source Engine.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In the video game &quot;Splatoon&quot;, the playable characters were originally going to be rabbits instead of squids.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In the game Dead by Daylight, the killer Michael Myers is refered to as &quot;The Shape&quot;.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"The ultimate phrase used by Pharah from Overwatch is: &quot;Justice rains from above!&quot;","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"Peter Molyneux was the founder of Bullfrog Productions.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"The 2005 video game &quot;Call of Duty 2: Big Red One&quot; is not available on PC.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"The Indie Game Development Studio Cing, developers of Hotel Dusk and Last Window, went bankrupt on March 1st, 2010.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"Several characters in &quot;Super Mario 64&quot; blink their eyes, including Mario himself.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"&quot;Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater&quot; was released in 2004.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In Pok&eacute;mon, Arbok evolves into Seviper.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]}]